Hey everybody, I'm Amanda and this is Small Doses Podcast.
And today I get the opportunity to speak to just like a living intellectual civil rights icon.
Sherilyn Ifill will be joining us, the former head of the NAACP Legal Defense Fund.
Just casually the endowed chair of civil rights at Howard University.
And we will be talking about side effects of civil rights.
This is your opportunity to ask like an actual living legend her thoughts on civil rights.
Where we were, where we are, where we're going.
So drop your questions in the comments.
Your girls with the intellectuals.
You see my lawyer outfit.
Drop them in the comments.